Hi! welcome back.
I hope the first quiz
wasn't too easy
and wasn't too difficult.
Let's look at the quiz.
______ name is Lili.
Lili
My name is Lili.
or
I'm name is Lili.
which one?
Let's look.
My name is Lili.
Yeah.
So, we say "My name is (name)."
If we want to say "I'm",
we can say "I'm Lili."
But we can not say
I'm name.
It's not right.
I'm Lili.
or
My name is Lili.
_______ we can call this "blank."
So,
__________ from China.
My from China.
or
I'm from China.
I am from China.
Both are okay.
I am from America.
Where is this?
What is this?
I am from America.
Yeah, this is America
You are from Korea.
Or Mexico?
Where is this?
Korea or Mexico?
That is Korea.
She is from Japan.
She is from Mexico.
Where is this?
Is this Mexico?
or Japan?
She is from Mexico.
Yeah, this is Mexico.
What is your name?
I'm from China.
or
I'm Emma.
So, we have "What is your name?"
Which one is it?
It's "I'm Emma."
Yeah, we can say
I'm Emma.
We can say
I am Emma.
and My name is Emma.
What question we can ask for
if we want the answer
I'm from China?
How can we ask?
We can say
Where are you from?
I'm from China
is okay,
but "What is your name?"
Name, we want "Emma."
Or I'm Josh.
Where are you from?
yeah
Which one is it?
I'm from China.
yeah
So, I want you to type.
Tell me:
What is your name?
Where are you from?
Okay?
I want to know.